Guide to the Brooklyn Historical Society newspaper collection ARC.258
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Long Island Weekly Star (Long Island City, New York) (microfilm), January 4, 1901 – December 28, 1906 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Long Island Weekly Star (Long Island City, New York) (microfilm), 1916 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Long Islander (Huntington, New York) (microfilm), July 12, 1839 – July 12, 1901 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Nassau Post (Freeport, New York) (microfilm), January 1914 – July 1918 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- National Police Gazette, The (New York, New York), January 18, 1913 (Box 19)
  Sports journal
- Neighbors & Merchants / Vecinos & Commerciantes, 1985-1986 (Box 56)
  Cypress Hills community. In Spanish and English.
- New Amsterdam Gazette, January 10, 1888 (Supplement); September 17-October 31, 1888 (Extra Edition) (Box 19)
- New Brooklyn Quarterly, Summer 1982 (Box 51)
- New York Harbor Watch (four bound volumes), 2001-2004 (Volume Library gallery shelf 31.1.F)
  Greater New York military community
- New York Mail and Express supplement - Illustrated Saturday Magazine, July 1, 1899 (Box 19)
- New-York Packet and the American Advertiser, April 3, 1783 (Box 19)
- New-York Packet, November 2, 1787 (Box 19)
- New York Times, The, May 2, 1862 (Box 2)
- New-York Tribune, August 5, 1865 (Box 2)
- New Yorkin Uutiset, September 9, 1986 (Box 55)
  Finnish language.
- Newspaper, The, May 1983 (Box 51)
  Carroll Gardens and Cobble Hill
- Newtown Register Weekly (microfilm), July 17, 1873 – June 1, 1935 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Nuevo Amanecer, November 7, 1987 (Box 42)
  Spanish language. "El periodico del la communidad Catolica por The Tablet".
- Norden, January 14, 1988 (Box 42)
  English and Finnish language.
- Nordstjernan Svea, January 21, 1988 (Box 42)
  "Swedish News"
- North Hempstead Gazette (Roslyn, Long Island), October 5, 1848 (Box 6)
- North Hempstead Times (Great Neck, Long Island), August 13, 1898 (Box 6)
- Northport Journal (microfilm), January 6, 1922 – June 26, 1925 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Northport Journal (microfilm), September 9, 1932 – December 9, 1933 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Norway Times, October 8, 1987 (Box 42)
  English and Norwegian language.
- Nowy Dziennik, December 20, 1988 (Box 55)
  Polish language.
- Orange Patrol (Goshen, New York), April 7, 1801 (Box 19)
- Our Time Press, March 1996; May 2004; June 16, 2007 (Box 39)
  African-American businesses and customers
- Park Slope Courier, August 4-17, 1994; May 31, June 14, August 9, 16, 1999 (Box 39)
  Park Slope, Windsor Terrace, Prospect Heights, Gowanus
- Park Slope Courier (six bound volumes), January 2001 - September 2002 (Volume Library gallery shelf 31.1.F)
- Park Slope Courier (sixteen bound volumes), October 2002 - December 2005 (Volume Library gallery shelf 31.1.G)
- Park Slope Courier, January 28 - February 3, 2011; December 9-15, 2016 (Box 39)
- Park Slope Jewish Review, 1988 (Box 39)
  Congregation B'nai Jacob
- Park Slope Paper, The, January 10, 2000 (Box 39)
- Park Slope Paper, The (Windsor Terrace Edition), June 25, 1999
- Peoples Tribune, 1985 (Box 39)
- Phoenix, The (Brooklyn Bridge anniversary supplement), May 26, 1983 (Box 56)
- Phoenix, December 1, 1988 (Box 39)
  Section 2 only. See also: Brooklyn, Inc
- Phoenix, March 25, August 2, 1996; May 15, May 29, June 5, November 13, 1998 (Box 39)
  "Brownstone Brooklyn"
- Picket, The (Rockville Centre, New York) (microfilm), July 7, 1865 – June 12, 1868 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Picket, The (Rockville Centre, New York) (microfilm), June 25, 1869 – June 10, 1870 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Political Intelligencer, and New-Jersey Advertiser, The (New Brunswick, New Jersey), September 21, 1784 (Box 19)
- Port Jefferson Echo (microfilm), August 6, 1892 - December 25, 1931 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Port Jefferson Times (microfilm), March 15, 1879 – September 9, 1905; April 17, 1915 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Prospect Press, The (Park Slope edition), December 23, 1982 - December 22, 1983 (Box 50)
- Queens County Sentinel (Hempstead, New York) (microfilm), June 3, 1858 – May 26, 1898 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Queens County Sentinel (Hempstead, New York) (microfilm), June 1, 1899 – May 25, 1922 (Cabinet Microfilm)
  Various issues, not a complete run
- Red Hook Star-Review, The, November 2010 - May 2011; January-May 2013 (Box 39)
- Red Hook Star-Review, The, February 2017 (Box 56)
- Republican Watchman (Greenport, New York), August 28, 1858; 1876 (Box 31)
  1876 issues are very fragile; not a complete run
- Rockaway News (Far Rockaway, New York) (microfilm), February 11, 1903 – January 14, 1905 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Shipbuilder, The (Brooklyn, New York) (microfilm), 1941-1966 (Cabinet Microfilm)
  Brooklyn Navy Yard newspaper
- Shopper, The, July 1984; February 1989 (Box 42)
  "A neighborhood magazine of shops, services, previews, reviews and lifestyles"
- Smarter Shopper, The, January 1990 (Box 51)
  Fort Greene and surrounding neighborhoods
- Southside Observer (Rockville Centre, New York) (microfilm), February 1882 – November 1920 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Southside Signal (Babylon, New York) (microfilm), July 7, 1869 – June 30, 1920 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Spirit of Flatbush, The, Fall 1989; Fall 1991 (Box 51)
- Spring Creek Sun, July 1999 - February 2012 (Box 50, Box 59, Item February 2010 - February 2012)
  East New York; Not a complete run
- Staten Island Star Reporter (six bound volumes), 2001-2005 (Volume Library gallery shelf 31.1.H)
- Suffolk Bulletin (Huntington, New York) (microfilm), January 4, 1918 – December 26, 1919 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Suffolk Bulletin (Huntington, New York) (microfilm), January 6, 1922 – December 28, 1923 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Suffolk Bulletin (Huntington, New York) (microfilm), January 2, 1925 – December 28, 1927 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Suffolk County News (Sayville, New York) (microfilm), January 7, 1888 – July 10, 1942 (Cabinet Microfilm)
- Suffolk Weekly Gazette, The, January 3, 1851 - November 20, 1857 (Box 6)
- Sun, The (New York), September 3, 1833 (Box 19)
- Sunset Park Shopping & Neighborhood News, December 1979 (Box 42)
- Tablet, The, January 1 - December 24, 1983; July 3 - August 14, 1999 (Box 51)
  Roman Catholic Diocese of Brooklyn; Also includes Queens
- Trench and Camp, 1919 (Box 19)
- Ulster County Gazette (Kingston, New York), January 4, 1800 (Box 19)
- WaterfrontWeek (Brooklyn, NY), 1999-2002 (Box 58)
- Weekblad of Brielsche Courant, August 14, 1888 (Box 31)
  Regarding Holland Society of New York; in Dutch and English
- Whip and Satirist of New-York and Brooklyn, April 30, 1842 (Box 31)